<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation – SQL Reporting Services Integration with MS SharePoint</title>
    <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/reportingservices/sql-reporting-services-integration-with-ms-sharepoint/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SQL Reporting Services Integration with MS SharePoint on Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/reportingservices/sql-reporting-services-integration-with-ms-sharepoint/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reportingservices: Introduction</title>
      <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/reportingservices/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/reportingservices/introduction/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;

Aspose.PDF for Reporting Services has been very remarkable for PDF generation through SQL Reporting Services since many years and it provides diverse configuration and parameterization options which are not supported by default in SQL Reporting Services. Recently we have received some requested regarding Aspose.PDF for Reporting Services Integration with SharePoint. For this article, we are going to focus on MS SharePoint 2010. Before we proceed further, we assume that you already have a SharePoint Farm setup. In this example we are going to use full SharePoint Cloud. However the steps are similar for SharePoint Foundation Server.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we proceed further, let’s take a look over reference topics that we have consulted during the preparation of this article.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/bb326358.aspx&#34;&gt;Overview of Reporting Services and SharePoint Technology Integration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/bb510781.aspx&#34;&gt;Deployment Topologies for Reporting Services in SharePoint Integrated Mode&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/bb326356.aspx&#34;&gt;Configuring Reporting Services for SharePoint 2010 Integration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;environment-setup-out-setup-consists-of-4-servers-it-includes-of-a-domain-controller-a-sql-server-a-sharepoint-server-and-a-server-for-reporting-services-you-may-opt-to-have-sharepoint-and-reporting-services-on-the-same-box-which-will-simplify-this-a-bit-and-i-will-point-out-some-of-the-differences&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environment Setup Out setup consists of 4 servers. It includes of a Domain Controller, a SQL Server, a SharePoint Server and a server for Reporting Services. You may opt to have SharePoint and Reporting Services on the same box, which will simplify this a bit and I will point out some of the differences.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;installation-pre-requisites-hahahugoshortcode-s1-hbhb&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Installation Pre-Requisites 

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;

The Reporting Services Add-In for SharePoint is one of the key components to getting Integration working properly. The Add-In needs to be installed on any of the Web Front Ends (WFE) that is in your SharePoint farm along with the Central Admin server. One of the new changes with SQL 2008 R2 &amp;amp; SharePoint 2010 is that the 2008 R2 Add-In is now a pre-requisite for the SharePoint Install. This means that the RS Add-In will be laid down when you go to install SharePoint. It has been shown and highlighted in figure below. This actually avoids a lot of issues we saw with SP 2007 and RS 2008 when installing the Add-In. &lt;img src=&#34;introduction_1.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image1 :- Reporting Services Add-in for Share Point
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;sharepoint-authentication-before-we-jump-into-the-rs-integration-pieces-one-thing-i-want-to-point-out-about-the-sharepoint-farm-is-how-you-setup-the-site-more-specifically-how-you-configure-authentication-for-the-site-whether-it-will-be-classic-or-claims-this-choice-is-important-in-the-beginning-i-dont-believe-that-you-can-change-this-option-once-it-is-done-if-you-can-change-it-it-would-not-be-a-simple-process-note-reporting-services-2008-r2-is-not-claims-aware-even-if-you-choose-your-sharepoint-site-to-use-claims-reporting-services-itself-isnt-claims-aware-that-said-it-does-affect-how-authentication-works-with-reporting-services-so-what-is-the-difference-from-a-reporting-services-perspective-it-comes-down-to-whether-you-want-to-forward-user-credentials-to-the-data-source-classic--can-use-kerberos-and-forward-the-users-credentials-to-your-back-end-datasource-will-need-to-use-kerberos-for-that-claims--a-claims-token-is-used-and-not-a-windows-token-rs-will-always-use-trusted-authentication-in-this-scenario-and-will-only-have-access-to-the-spuser-token-you-will-need-to-store-your-credentials-within-your-data-source-for-now-we-just-want-to-focus-on-setup-of-rs-at-this-point-sharepoint-is-installed-on-my-sharepoint-box-and-setup-with-a-classic-auth-site-on-port-80-on-the-rs-server-i-have-just-installed-reporting-services-and-thats-it&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SharePoint Authentication Before we jump into the RS Integration pieces, one thing I want to point out about the SharePoint Farm is how you setup the Site. More specifically how you configure authentication for the site. Whether it will be Classic or Claims. This choice is important in the beginning. I don&amp;rsquo;t believe that you can change this option once it is done. If you can change it, it would not be a simple process. NOTE: Reporting Services 2008 R2 is NOT Claims aware Even if you choose your SharePoint site to use Claims, Reporting Services itself isn&amp;rsquo;t Claims aware. That said, it does affect how authentication works with Reporting Services. So, what is the difference from a Reporting Services perspective? It comes down to whether you want to forward User Credentials to the data source. Classic:- Can use Kerberos and forward the user&amp;rsquo;s credentials to your back end datasource (will need to use Kerberos for that). Claims:- A Claims token is used and not a windows token. RS will always use Trusted Authentication in this scenario and will only have access to the SPUser token. You will need to store your credentials within your data source. For now we just want to focus on setup of RS. At this point SharePoint is installed on my SharePoint Box and setup with a Classic Auth Site on port 80. On the RS Server I have just installed Reporting Services and that&amp;rsquo;s it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reportingservices: Setting up Reporting Services</title>
      <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/reportingservices/setting-up-reporting-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/reportingservices/setting-up-reporting-services/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;

Our first stop on the Reporting Services Server is the Reporting Services Configuration Manager.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;service-account-be-sure-to-understand-what-service-account-you-are-using-for-reporting-services-if-we-run-into-issues-it-may-be-related-to-the-service-account-you-are-using-the-default-is-network-service-when-we-go-to-deploy-new-builds-we-always-use-domain-accounts-because-that-is-where-we-are-likely-to-hit-issues-for-this-instance-of-server-we-have-used-a-domain-account-called-rsservice-todoimage_alt_textsetting-up-reporting-services_1png-image1--setting-up-service-account&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service Account: Be sure to understand what service account you are using for Reporting Services. If we run into issues, it may be related to the service account you are using. The default is Network Service. When we go to deploy new builds, we always use Domain Accounts, because that is where we are likely to hit issues. For this instance of server, we have used a Domain Account called RSService. &lt;img src=&#34;setting-up-reporting-services_1.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image1:- Setting-up service account&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;web-service-url-hahahugoshortcode-s1-hbhb&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Web Service URL: 

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;

We will need to configure the Web Service URL. This is the ReportServer virtual directory (vdir) that hosts the Web Services Reporting Services uses, and what SharePoint will communicate with. Unless you want to customize the properties of the vdir (i.e. SSL, ports, host headers, etc…), you should just be able to click Apply here and be good to go. &lt;img src=&#34;setting-up-reporting-services_2.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image2:- Setting up Web Service URL Once Web service URL have been setup, you should able to see the following results &lt;img src=&#34;setting-up-reporting-services_3.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image3:- Successful setup of Web service URL
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;database-we-need-to-create-the-reporting-services-catalog-database-this-can-be-placed-on-any-sql-2008-or-sql-2008-r2-database-engine-sql11-would-work-ok-as-well-but-that-is-still-in-beta-this-action-will-create-two-databases-reportserver-and-reportservertempdb-by-default-the-other-important-step-with-this-is-to-make-sure-that-you-choose-sharepoint-integrated-for-the-database-type-once-this-choice-is-made-it-cannot-be-changed-todoimage_alt_textsetting-up-reporting-services_4png-image4--creating-report-server-database-todoimage_alt_textsetting-up-reporting-services_5png-image5--setting-up-database-server-and-authentication-type-todoimage_alt_textsetting-up-reporting-services_6png-image6--setting-up-database-name-and-mode-for-the-credentials-this-is-how-the-report-server-will-communicate-with-the-sql-server-whatever-account-you-select-will-be-given-certain-rights-within-the-catalog-database-as-well-as-a-few-of-the-system-databases-via-the-rsexecrole-msdb-is-one-of-these-database-for-subscription-usage-as-we-make-use-of-sql-agent-todoimage_alt_textsetting-up-reporting-services_7png-image7--setting-up-report-server-database-credentials-once-database-credentials-are-specified-we-should-be-able-to-get-the-results-as-specified-below-todoimage_alt_textsetting-up-reporting-services_8png-image8--report-server-database-creation-progress-todoimage_alt_textsetting-up-reporting-services_9png-image9--report-server-database-completion-summary&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Database: We need to create the Reporting Services Catalog Database. This can be placed on any SQL 2008 or SQL 2008 R2 Database Engine. SQL11 would work ok as well, but that is still in BETA. This action will create two databases, ReportServer and ReportServerTempDB, by default. The other important step with this is to make sure that you choose SharePoint Integrated for the database type. Once this choice is made, it cannot be changed. &lt;img src=&#34;setting-up-reporting-services_4.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image4:- Creating report server database &lt;img src=&#34;setting-up-reporting-services_5.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image5:- Setting up database server and authentication type &lt;img src=&#34;setting-up-reporting-services_6.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image6:- Setting up database name and Mode For the credentials, this is how the Report Server will communicate with the SQL Server. Whatever account you select, will be given certain rights within the Catalog database as well as a few of the system databases via the RSExecRole. MSDB is one of these database for Subscription usage as we make use of SQL Agent. &lt;img src=&#34;setting-up-reporting-services_7.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image7:- Setting up Report Server database credentials Once database credentials are specified, we should be able to get the results as specified below. &lt;img src=&#34;setting-up-reporting-services_8.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image8:- Report Server database creation progress &lt;img src=&#34;setting-up-reporting-services_9.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image9:- Report Server database completion summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;report-manager-url-hahahugoshortcode-s2-hbhb&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Report Manager URL: 

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;

We can skip the Report Manager URL as it isn’t used when we are in SharePoint Integrated mode. SharePoint is our frontend. Report Manager doesn’t work.
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;encryption-keys-backup-your-encryption-keys-and-make-sure-you-know-where-you-keep-them-if-you-get-into-a-situation-where-you-need-to-migrate-the-database-or-restore-it-you-will-need-these-todoimage_alt_textsetting-up-reporting-services_10png-image10--report-server-encryption-key-backup-congratulation-we-have-successfully-configured-reporting-services-using-configuration-manager-if-you-browse-to-the-url-on-the-web-service-url-tab-it-should-show-something-similar-to-the-following-todoimage_alt_textsetting-up-reporting-services_11png-image11--report-server-access-after-installation-reason-of-error-sharepoint-is-installed-on-our-wfe-and-we-finished-setting-up-reporting-services-in-this-example-reporting-services-and-sharepoint-are-on-different-machines-if-they-were-on-the-same-machine-you-wouldnt-have-seen-this-error-we-technically-need-to-install-sharepoint-on-the-rs-box-that-means-iis-will-be-enabled-as-well&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Encryption Keys: Backup your Encryption Keys and make sure you know where you keep them. If you get into a situation where you need to migrate the Database or restore it, you will need these. &lt;img src=&#34;setting-up-reporting-services_10.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image10:- Report Server Encryption key backup Congratulation! We have successfully configured Reporting Services using Configuration Manager. If you browse to the URL on the Web Service URL tab, it should show something similar to the following. &lt;img src=&#34;setting-up-reporting-services_11.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image11:- Report Server access after installation Reason of error: SharePoint is installed on our WFE and we finished setting up Reporting Services. In this example, Reporting Services and SharePoint are on different machines. If they were on the same machine, you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have seen this error. We technically need to install SharePoint on the RS Box. That means IIS will be enabled as well.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reportingservices: Setting up SharePoint on Reporting Services Server</title>
      <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/reportingservices/setting-up-sharepoint-on-reporting-services-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/reportingservices/setting-up-sharepoint-on-reporting-services-server/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;

Now we need to perform similar steps as we did for the SharePoint WFE. First thing is to go through the Prereq uisites install and once it is done, startup the SharePoint setup.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the setup I choose Server Farm and a complete install to match my SharePoint Box, as I do not want a standalone install for SharePoint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;sharepoint-configuration-in-the-sharepoint-configuration-wizard-we-want-to-connect-to-an-existing-farm-todoimage_alt_textsetting-up-sharepoint-on-reporting-services-server_1png-image1--sharepoint-configuration-wizard-we-will-then-point-it-to-the-sharepoint_config-database-that-our-farm-is-using-if-you-dont-know-where-this-is-you-can-find-out-through-central-admin-through-system-settings---manager-servers-in-this-farm-todoimage_alt_textsetting-up-sharepoint-on-reporting-services-server_2png-image2--specify-database-configuration-settings-todoimage_alt_textsetting-up-sharepoint-on-reporting-services-server_3png-image3--sharepoint-configuration-wizard-once-the-wizard-is-done-that-is-all-we-need-to-do-on-the-report-server-box-for-now-going-back-to-the-reportserver-url-we-will-see-another-error-but-that-is-because-we-have-not-configured-it-through-central-administrator-todoimage_alt_textsetting-up-sharepoint-on-reporting-services-server_4png-image4--report-server-error&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SharePoint Configuration In the SharePoint Configuration Wizard, we want to connect to an existing farm. &lt;img src=&#34;setting-up-sharepoint-on-reporting-services-server_1.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image1:- SharePoint configuration wizard We will then point it to the SharePoint_Config database that our farm is using. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know where this is, you can find out through Central Admin through System Settings -&amp;gt; Manager Servers in this farm. &lt;img src=&#34;setting-up-sharepoint-on-reporting-services-server_2.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image2:- Specify database configuration settings &lt;img src=&#34;setting-up-sharepoint-on-reporting-services-server_3.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image3:- SharePoint configuration wizard Once the wizard is done, that is all we need to do on the Report Server Box for now. Going back to the ReportServer URL, we will see another error, but that is because we have not configured it through Central Administrator. &lt;img src=&#34;setting-up-sharepoint-on-reporting-services-server_4.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image4:- Report server error&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reportingservices: Reporting Services and SharePoint configuration</title>
      <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/reportingservices/reporting-services-and-sharepoint-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/reportingservices/reporting-services-and-sharepoint-configuration/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;

Now that SharePoint is installed and configured on the RS server and RS is setup and setup through the Reporting Services Configuration Manager, we can move onto the configuration within Central Admin. RS 2008 R2 has really simplified this process. We use to have a 3 step process that you had to perform to get this to work. Now we just have one step.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want to go to the Central Administrator Web site and then into General Application Settings. Towards the bottom we will see Reporting Services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;reporting-services-and-sharepoint-configuration_1.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image1&lt;/strong&gt;:- SharePoint configuration dialog&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Select &amp;ldquo;Reporting Services Integration&amp;rdquo; link. Following screen will be displayed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;reporting-services-and-sharepoint-configuration_2.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image2&lt;/strong&gt;:- Specify Reporting Services integration credentials&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;web-service-url-we-will-provide-the-url-for-the-report-server-that-we-found-in-the-reporting-services-configuration-manager&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Web Service URL: We will provide the URL for the Report Server that we found in the Reporting Services Configuration Manager.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;authentication-mode-hahahugoshortcode-s1-hbhb-in-short-if-your-site-is-using-claims-authentication-you-will-always-be-using-trusted-authentication-regardless-of-what-you-choose-here-if-you-want-to-pass-windows-credentials-you-will-want-to-choose-windows-authentication-for-trusted-authentication-we-will-pass-the-spuser-token-and-not-rely-on-the-windows-credential-you-will-also-want-to-use-trusted-authentication-if-you-have-configured-your-classic-mode-sites-for-ntlm-and-rs-is-setup-for-ntlm-kerberos-would-be-needed-to-use-windows-authentication-and-to-pass-that-through-for-your-data-source&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Authentication Mode: 

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;

We will also select an Authentication Mode. The following MSDN link goes through in detail what these are. Security Overview for Reporting Services in SharePoint Integrated Mode
&lt;/div&gt;
 In short, if your site is using Claims Authentication, you will always be using Trusted Authentication regardless of what you choose here. If you want to pass windows credentials, you will want to choose Windows Authentication. For Trusted Authentication, we will pass the SPUser token and not rely on the Windows credential. You will also want to use Trusted Authentication if you have configured your Classic Mode sites for NTLM and RS is setup for NTLM. Kerberos would be needed to use Windows Authentication and to pass that through for your data source.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&#34;activate-feature-this-gives-you-an-option-of-activating-the-reporting-services-on-all-site-collections-or-you-can-choose-which-ones-you-want-to-activate-it-on-this-just-really-means-which-sites-will-be-able-to-use-reporting-services-when-it-is-done-you-should-see-the-following-results-todoimage_alt_textreporting-services-and-sharepoint-configuration_3png-image3--successful-integration-of-reporting-services-with-sharepoint-environment-going-back-to-the-reportserver-url-we-should-see-something-similar-to-the-following-todoimage_alt_textreporting-services-and-sharepoint-configuration_4png-image4--reporting-services-is-successfully-connected-with-sharepoint-environment-note-if-your-sharepoint-site-is-configured-for-ssl-it-wont-show-up-in-this-list-it-is-a-known-issue-and-doesnt-mean-there-is-a-problem-your-reports-should-still-work-now-that-we-have-successfully-integrated-both-products-we-are-ready-to-use-reporting-services-in-sharepoint-2010-as-the-previous-version-we-have-a-feature-activated-when-we-configure-reporting-services-integration-in-the-site-collection-feature-also-the-installation-added-3-content-types-to-add-to-our-site-in-image-7-we-can-see-2-of-them-content-types-added-in-a-document-library-to-create-a-custom-report-us-ing-the-as-we-can-see-in-image5-below-todoimage_alt_textreporting-services-and-sharepoint-configuration_5png-image5--report-builder-the-reporter-builder-is-an-activex-control-so-we-need-to-download-it-over-the-server-as-we-can-see-in-image-6-below-todoimage_alt_textreporting-services-and-sharepoint-configuration_6png-image6--download-and-install-report-builder-once-the-download-process-is-completed-load-the-report-builder-control-now-we-are-ready-to-design-our-first-report-as-shown-in-image7-below-todoimage_alt_textreporting-services-and-sharepoint-configuration_7png-image7--report-builder--new-report-generation-wizard-after-create-our-report-we-could-save-it-in-the-document-library-created-to-put-the-reports-in-our-sharepoint-2010-the-other-content-type-must-be-used-to-create-shared-connection-as-data-source-and-save-them-in-a-document-library-in-sharepoint-we-can-create-a-document-library-add-this-content-type-and-after-we-can-have-our-connections-available-to-change-the-data-source-of-the-reports-todoimage_alt_textreporting-services-and-sharepoint-configuration_8png-image8--successful-integration-of-asposepdf-for-reporting-services-with-ms-sharepoint&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Activate feature: This gives you an option of activating the Reporting Services on all Site collections, or you can choose which ones you want to activate it on. This just really means which sites will be able to use Reporting Services. When it is done, you should see the following results &lt;img src=&#34;reporting-services-and-sharepoint-configuration_3.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image3:- Successful integration of Reporting Services with SharePoint environment Going back to the ReportServer URL, we should see something similar to the following &lt;img src=&#34;reporting-services-and-sharepoint-configuration_4.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image4:- Reporting Services is successfully connected with SharePoint environment NOTE: If your SharePoint site is configured for SSL, it won&amp;rsquo;t show up in this list. It is a known issue and doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean there is a problem. Your reports should still work. Now that we have successfully integrated both products, we are ready to use Reporting Services in SharePoint 2010. As the previous version we have a feature (activated when we configure Reporting Services Integration) in the “Site Collection Feature”. Also the installation added 3 content types to add to our site. In Image 7 we can see 2 of them content types added in a document library to create a custom report us ing the, as we can see in Image5 below. &lt;img src=&#34;reporting-services-and-sharepoint-configuration_5.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image5:- Report Builder The “Reporter Builder” is an ActiveX control so we need to download it over the server, as we can see in Image 6 below. &lt;img src=&#34;reporting-services-and-sharepoint-configuration_6.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image6:- Download and install Report Builder Once the download process is completed, load the “Report Builder” control. Now we are ready to design our first report, as shown in Image7 below. &lt;img src=&#34;reporting-services-and-sharepoint-configuration_7.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image7:- Report Builder – New Report generation wizard After create our report we could save it in the document library created to put the reports in our SharePoint 2010. The other content type must be used to create shared connection as data source and save them in a document library in SharePoint. We can create a document library, add this content type and after we can have our connections available to change the data source of the reports. &lt;img src=&#34;reporting-services-and-sharepoint-configuration_8.png&#34; alt=&#34;todo:image_alt_text&#34;&gt; Image8:- Successful Integration of Aspose.PDF for Reporting Services with MS SharePoint&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
