<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation – Working with Stamps and Watermarks</title>
    <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/net/working-with-stamps-and-watermarks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Working with Stamps and Watermarks on Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/net/working-with-stamps-and-watermarks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Net: Adding Stamp in a PDF file</title>
      <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/net/adding-stamp-in-a-pdf-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/net/adding-stamp-in-a-pdf-file/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h2 id=&#34;adding-image-stamp-in-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adding Image Stamp in PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can check how to add a stamp using Aspose.PDF and get the results online at this link:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://products.aspose.app/pdf/watermark&#34;&gt;products.aspose.app/pdf/watermark&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can use the ImageStamp class to add an image stamp to a PDF file. The ImageStamp class provides the properties necessary for creating an image-based stamp, such as height, width, opacity and so on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To add an image stamp:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a Document object and an ImageStamp object using required properties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Call the Page class&amp;rsquo; AddStamp method to add the stamp to the PDF.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following code snippet shows how to add image stamp in the PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/7e1330795d76012fcb04248bb81d45b3.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePDF-Stamps-Watermarks-AddImageStamp-AddImageStamp.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;control-image-quality-when-adding-a-stamp&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Control Image Quality when Adding a Stamp&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When adding an image as a stamp object, you can control the quality of the image. The Quality property of the ImageStamp class is used for this purpose. It indicates the quality of image in percents (valid values are 0..100).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/7e1330795d76012fcb04248bb81d45b3.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePDF-Stamps-Watermarks-AddImageStamp-ControlImageQuality.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;adding-pdf-page-stamp-in-the-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adding PDF Page Stamp in the PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use &lt;strong&gt;PdfPageStamp&lt;/strong&gt; class to add a PDF page as stamp in a PDF file. &lt;strong&gt;PdfPageStamp&lt;/strong&gt; class provides properties necessary to create a PDF page based stamp. You can pass a particular page of any PDF file to the constructor of &lt;strong&gt;PdfPageStamp&lt;/strong&gt; class. In order to add page based stamp, you need to create a &lt;strong&gt;Document&lt;/strong&gt; object and a &lt;strong&gt;PdfPageStamp&lt;/strong&gt; object using required properties. After that, you can call &lt;strong&gt;AddStamp&lt;/strong&gt; method of the &lt;strong&gt;Page&lt;/strong&gt; to add the stamp in the PDF. The following code snippet shows you how to add PDF page stamp in a PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/7e1330795d76012fcb04248bb81d45b3.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePDF-Stamps-Watermarks-AddPDFPageStamp-PDFPageStamp.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;add-page-number-stamp-in-a-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Page Number Stamp in a PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use &lt;strong&gt;PageNumber&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Stamp&lt;/strong&gt; class to add a page number stamp in a PDF file. &lt;strong&gt;PageNumber&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Stamp&lt;/strong&gt; class provides properties necessary to create a page number based stamp like format, margins, alignments, starting number etc. In order to add page number stamp, you need to create a &lt;strong&gt;Document&lt;/strong&gt; object and a &lt;strong&gt;PageNumber&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Stamp&lt;/strong&gt; object using required properties. After that, you can call &lt;strong&gt;AddStamp&lt;/strong&gt; method of the &lt;strong&gt;Page&lt;/strong&gt; to add the stamp in the PDF. You can also set the font attributes of the page number stamp. The following code snippet shows you how to add page numbers in a PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/7e1330795d76012fcb04248bb81d45b3.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePDF-Stamps-Watermarks-PageNumberStamps-PageNumberStamps.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;adding-date-time-stamp-in-pdf&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adding Date-Time Stamp in PDF&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use &lt;strong&gt;TextStamp&lt;/strong&gt; class to add a text stamp in a PDF file. &lt;strong&gt;TextStamp&lt;/strong&gt; class provides properties necessary to create a text based stamp like font size, font style, and font color etc. In order to add text stamp, you need to create a &lt;strong&gt;Document&lt;/strong&gt; object and a &lt;strong&gt;TextStamp&lt;/strong&gt; object using required properties. After that, you can call &lt;strong&gt;AddStamp&lt;/strong&gt; method of the &lt;strong&gt;Page&lt;/strong&gt; to add the stamp in the PDF. 
The following code snippet shows you how to add text stamp in the PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/7e1330795d76012fcb04248bb81d45b3.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePDF-Stamps-Watermarks-AddDateTimeStamp-AddDateTimeStamp.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;adding-text-stamp-in-the-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adding Text Stamp in the PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use &lt;strong&gt;TextStamp&lt;/strong&gt; class to add a text stamp in a PDF file. &lt;strong&gt;TextStamp&lt;/strong&gt; class provides properties necessary to create a text based stamp like font size, font style, and font color etc. In order to add text stamp, you need to create a &lt;strong&gt;Document&lt;/strong&gt; object and a &lt;strong&gt;TextStamp&lt;/strong&gt; object using required properties. After that, you can call &lt;strong&gt;AddStamp&lt;/strong&gt; method of the &lt;strong&gt;Page&lt;/strong&gt; to add the stamp in the PDF. 
The following code snippet shows you how to add text stamp in the PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/7e1330795d76012fcb04248bb81d45b3.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePDF-Stamps-Watermarks-AddTextStamp-AddTextStamp.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;define-alignment-for-textstamp-object&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Define alignment for TextStamp object&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adding watermarks to PDF documents is one of the frequent demanded features and Aspose.PDF for .NET is fully capable of adding Image as well as Text watermarks. We have a class named TextStamp which provides the feature to add text stamps over the PDF file. Recently there has been a requirement to support the feature to specify the alignment of text when using TextStamp object. So in order to fulfill this requirement, we have introduced &lt;strong&gt;TextAlignment&lt;/strong&gt; property in &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.aspose.com/api/net/pdf/aspose.pdf/textstamp&#34;&gt;TextStamp&lt;/a&gt; class. Using this property, we can specify the Horizontal text alignment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following code snippets shows an example on how to load an existing PDF document and add TextStamp over it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/7e1330795d76012fcb04248bb81d45b3.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePDF-Stamps-Watermarks-DefineAlignment-DefineAlignment.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;fill-stroke-text-as-stamp-in-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fill Stroke Text as Stamp in PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have implemented setting of rendering mode for text adding and editing scenarios. To render stroke text please create TextState object and set RenderingMode to TextRenderingMode.StrokeText and also select color for StrokingColor property. Later, bind TextState to the stamp using BindTextState() method.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following code snippet demonstrates adding Fill Stroke Text:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/7e1330795d76012fcb04248bb81d45b3.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePDF-Stamps-Watermarks-FillStrokeText-1.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;add-image-stamp-as-background-in-floating-box&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Image Stamp as Background in Floating Box&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aspose.PDF API lets you add image stamp as background in a floating box. The BackgroundImage property of FloatingBox class can be used to set the background image stamp for a floating box as shown in following code sample.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-com-gists/63473b1ba28e09e229cfbf4430eabd8a.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePDF-Stamps-Watermarks-AddImageStamp-AddImageStampAsBackgroundInFloatingBox.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Net: Manage Header and Footer of PDF File</title>
      <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/net/manage-header-and-footer-of-pdf-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/net/manage-header-and-footer-of-pdf-file/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h2 id=&#34;adding-text-in-header-of-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adding Text in Header of PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use &lt;strong&gt;TextStamp&lt;/strong&gt; class to add text in the header of a PDF file. &lt;strong&gt;TextStamp&lt;/strong&gt; class provides properties necessary to create a text based stamp like font size, font style, and font color etc. In order to add text in the header, you need to create a &lt;strong&gt;Document&lt;/strong&gt; object and a &lt;strong&gt;TextStamp&lt;/strong&gt; object using required properties. After that, you can call &lt;strong&gt;AddStamp&lt;/strong&gt; method of the &lt;strong&gt;Page&lt;/strong&gt; to add the text in the header of the PDF.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You need to set the &lt;strong&gt;TopMargin&lt;/strong&gt; property in such a way that it adjusts the text in the header area of your PDF. You also need to set &lt;strong&gt;HorizontalAlignment&lt;/strong&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;Center&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;VerticalAlignment&lt;/strong&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;Top&lt;/strong&gt;. The following code snippet shows you how to add text in the header of a PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/7e1330795d76012fcb04248bb81d45b3.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePDF-Stamps-Watermarks-TextinHeader-TextinHeader.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;adding-text-in-footer-of-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adding Text in Footer of PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use &lt;strong&gt;TextStamp&lt;/strong&gt; class to add text in the footer of a PDF file. &lt;strong&gt;TextStamp&lt;/strong&gt; class provides properties necessary to create a text based stamp like font size, font style, and font color etc. In order to add text in the footer, you need to create a &lt;strong&gt;Document&lt;/strong&gt; object and a &lt;strong&gt;TextStamp&lt;/strong&gt; object using required properties. After that, you can call &lt;strong&gt;AddStamp&lt;/strong&gt; method of the &lt;strong&gt;Page&lt;/strong&gt; to add the text in the footer of the PDF.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;

You need to set the &lt;strong&gt;Bottom&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Margin&lt;/strong&gt; property in such a way that it adjusts the text in the footer area of your PDF. You also need to set &lt;strong&gt;HorizontalAlignment&lt;/strong&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;Center&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;VerticalAlignment&lt;/strong&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;Bottom&lt;/strong&gt; .
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following code snippet shows you how to add text in the footer of a PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/7e1330795d76012fcb04248bb81d45b3.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePDF-Stamps-Watermarks-TextinFooter-TextinFooter.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;adding-image-in-header-of-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adding Image in Header of PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use &lt;strong&gt;Image&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Stamp&lt;/strong&gt; class to add image in the header of a PDF file. &lt;strong&gt;Image&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Stamp&lt;/strong&gt; class provides properties necessary to create image based stamp like font size, font style, and font color etc. In order to add image in the header, you need to create a &lt;strong&gt;Document&lt;/strong&gt; object and a &lt;strong&gt;Image&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Stamp&lt;/strong&gt; object using required properties. After that, you can call &lt;strong&gt;AddStamp&lt;/strong&gt; method of the &lt;strong&gt;Page&lt;/strong&gt; to add the image in the header of the PDF.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;

You need to set the &lt;strong&gt;TopMargin&lt;/strong&gt; property in such a way that it adjusts the image in the header area of your PDF. You also need to set &lt;strong&gt;HorizontalAlignment&lt;/strong&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;Center&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;VerticalAlignment&lt;/strong&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;Top&lt;/strong&gt; .
&lt;/div&gt;
 
The following code snippet shows you how to add image in the header of a PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/7e1330795d76012fcb04248bb81d45b3.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePDF-Stamps-Watermarks-ImageinHeader-ImageinHeader.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;adding-image-in-footer-of-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adding Image in Footer of PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use &lt;strong&gt;Image&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Stamp&lt;/strong&gt; class to add image in the footer of a PDF file. &lt;strong&gt;Image&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Stamp&lt;/strong&gt; class provides properties necessary to create image based stamp like font size, font style, and font color etc. In order to add image in the footer, you need to create a &lt;strong&gt;Document&lt;/strong&gt; object and an &lt;strong&gt;Image&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Stamp&lt;/strong&gt; object using required properties. After that, you can call &lt;strong&gt;AddStamp&lt;/strong&gt; method of the &lt;strong&gt;Page&lt;/strong&gt; to add the image in the footer of the PDF.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;

You need to set the &lt;strong&gt;Bottom&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Margin&lt;/strong&gt; property in such a way that it adjusts the image in the footer area of your PDF. You also need to set &lt;strong&gt;HorizontalAlignment&lt;/strong&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;Center&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;VerticalAlignment&lt;/strong&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;Bottom&lt;/strong&gt; .
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following code snippet shows you how to add image in the footer of a PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/7e1330795d76012fcb04248bb81d45b3.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePDF-Stamps-Watermarks-ImageInFooter-ImageInFooter.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;adding-different-headers-in-one-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adding different Headers in one PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We know that we can add TextStamp in Header/Footer section of the document by using TopMargin or &lt;strong&gt;Bottom&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Margin&lt;/strong&gt; properties, but sometimes we may have the requirement to add multiple header/footers in a single PDF document. In order to accomplish this requirement, we will create individual TextStamp objects ( &lt;em&gt;number of objects depends upon the number of Header/Footers required&lt;/em&gt; )and will add them to PDF document. We may also specify different formatting information for individual stamp object. In following example, we have created &lt;strong&gt;Document&lt;/strong&gt; object and three &lt;strong&gt;TextStamp&lt;/strong&gt; objects and then we have used &lt;strong&gt;AddStamp&lt;/strong&gt; method of the &lt;strong&gt;Page&lt;/strong&gt; to add the text in the header section of the PDF. The following code snippet shows you how to add image in the footer of a PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/7e1330795d76012fcb04248bb81d45b3.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePDF-Stamps-Watermarks-AddingDifferentHeaders-AddingDifferentHeaders.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Net: Working with Existing Watermarks</title>
      <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/net/working-with-existing-watermarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/net/working-with-existing-watermarks/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h2 id=&#34;working-with-existing-watermarks&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Working with Existing Watermarks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A watermark created with Adobe Acrobat is called an artifact (as described in 14.8.2.2 Real Content and Artifacts of the PDF specification). In order to work with artifacts, Aspose.PDF has two classes: &lt;a href=&#34;https://apireference.aspose.com/net/pdf/aspose.pdf/artifact&#34;&gt;Artifact&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://apireference.aspose.com/net/pdf/aspose.pdf/artifactcollection&#34;&gt;ArtifactCollection&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to get all artifacts on a particular page, the &lt;a href=&#34;https://apireference.aspose.com/net/pdf/aspose.pdf/page&#34;&gt;Page&lt;/a&gt; class has the Artifacts property. This topic explains how to work with artifact in PDF files.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;working-with-artifacts&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Working with Artifacts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://apireference.aspose.com/net/pdf/aspose.pdf/artifact&#34;&gt;Artifact&lt;/a&gt; class contains following properties:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Artifact.Type&lt;/strong&gt; – gets the artifact type (supports values of the Artifact.ArtifactType enumeration where values include Background, Layout, Page, Pagination and Undefined).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Artifact.Subtype&lt;/strong&gt; – gets artifact subtype (supports the values of the Artifact.ArtifactSubtype enumeration where values include Background, Footer, Header, Undefined, Watermark).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;

Please note that watermarks created with Adobe Acrobat have the type Pagination and subtype Watermark.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Artifact.Contents&lt;/strong&gt; – Gets a collection of artifact internal operators. Its supported type is System.Collections.ICollection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Artifact.Form&lt;/strong&gt; – Gets an artifact&amp;rsquo;s XForm (if XForm is used). Watermarks, header, and footer artifacts contains XForm which shows all artifact contents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Artifact.Image&lt;/strong&gt; – Gets an artifact&amp;rsquo;s image (if an image is presents, else null).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Artifact.Text&lt;/strong&gt; – Gets an artifact&amp;rsquo;s text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Artifact.Rectangle&lt;/strong&gt; – Gets an position of an artifact on the page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Artifact.Rotation&lt;/strong&gt; – Gets an artifact&amp;rsquo;s rotation (in degrees, positive value indicates counter-clockwise rotation).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Artifact.Opacity&lt;/strong&gt; – Gets an artifact&amp;rsquo;s opacity. Possible values are in the range 0&amp;hellip;1, where 1 is completely opaque.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;programming-samples-getting-watermarks&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programming Samples: Getting Watermarks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following code snippet shows how to get each watermark on the first page of a PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/7e1330795d76012fcb04248bb81d45b3.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePDF-Stamps-Watermarks-GetWatermark-GetWatermark.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;programming-samples-counting-artifacts-of-a-particular-type&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programming Samples: Counting Artifacts of a Particular Type&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To calculate the total count of artifacts of a particular type (for example, the total number of watermarks), use the following code:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/7e1330795d76012fcb04248bb81d45b3.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePDF-Stamps-Watermarks-CountingArtifacts-CountingArtifacts.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
