<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation – Working with Bookmarks - Facades</title>
    <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/net/working-with-bookmarks-facades/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Working with Bookmarks - Facades on Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/net/working-with-bookmarks-facades/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Net: Create Bookmarks</title>
      <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/net/create-bookmarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/net/create-bookmarks/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h2 id=&#34;create-bookmarks-of-all-pages&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create Bookmarks of All Pages&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to create bookmarks of all the pages, you need to use &lt;strong&gt;CreateBookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; method without any parameters . &lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarEditor&lt;/strong&gt; class allows you to create bookmarks of all the pages of a PDF file. First, you need to create an object of &lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarkEditor&lt;/strong&gt; class and bind the input PDF using &lt;strong&gt;BindPdf&lt;/strong&gt; method. Then, you have to call &lt;strong&gt;CreateBookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; method and save the output PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;Save&lt;/strong&gt; method. The following code snippet shows you how to create Bookmarks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/4a12f0ebd453e7f0d552ed6658ed3253.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePdfFacades-Bookmarks-CreateBookmarksAll-CreateBookmarksAll.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;create-bookmarks-of-all-pages-with-properties&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create Bookmarks of All Pages with Properties&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarEditor&lt;/strong&gt; class allows you to create bookmarks of all the pages of a PDF file and specify the properties (Color, Bold, Italic). You can do that with the help of &lt;strong&gt;CreateBookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; method. First, you need to create an object of &lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarkEditor&lt;/strong&gt; class and bind the input PDF using &lt;strong&gt;BindPdf&lt;/strong&gt; method. Then, you have to call &lt;strong&gt;CreateBookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; method and save the output PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;Save&lt;/strong&gt; method. The following code snippet shows you how to create bookmarks of all the pages with properties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/4a12f0ebd453e7f0d552ed6658ed3253.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePdfFacades-Bookmarks-CreateBookmarksPagesProperties-CreateBookmarksPagesProperties.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;create-bookmark-of-a-particular-page&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create Bookmark of a Particular Page&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can create a bookmark of a particular page in an existing PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;CreateBookmarkOfPage&lt;/strong&gt; method. This method takes two arguments: bookmark title and page number. First, you need to create an object of &lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarkEditor&lt;/strong&gt; class and bind input PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;BindPdf&lt;/strong&gt; method. Then, you have to call the &lt;strong&gt;CreateBookmarkOfPage&lt;/strong&gt; method and save the output PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;Save&lt;/strong&gt; method. The following code snippet shows you how to create bookmark of a particular page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/4a12f0ebd453e7f0d552ed6658ed3253.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePdfFacades-Bookmarks-CreateBookmarkPage-CreateBookmarkPage.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;create-bookmarks-of-a-range-of-pages&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create Bookmarks of a Range of Pages&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarkEditor&lt;/strong&gt; class allows you to create bookmarks of a range of pages. You can use &lt;strong&gt;CreateBookmarkOfpage&lt;/strong&gt; method with two parameters: bookmark list (the list of the bookmark titles) and page list (the list of the pages to bookmark). First, you need to create an object of &lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarkEditor&lt;/strong&gt; class and bind the input PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;BindPdf&lt;/strong&gt; method. Then, you have to call &lt;strong&gt;CreateBookmarkOfPage&lt;/strong&gt; method and save the output PDF using &lt;strong&gt;Save&lt;/strong&gt; method. The following code snippet shows you how to create bookmarks of a range of pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/4a12f0ebd453e7f0d552ed6658ed3253.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePdfFacades-Bookmarks-CreateBookmarkPageRange-CreateBookmarkPageRange.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;add-bookmark-in-an-existing-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Bookmark in an Existing PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can add bookmark in an existing PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarkEditor&lt;/strong&gt; class. In order to create the bookmark, you need to create &lt;strong&gt;Bookmark&lt;/strong&gt; object and set the required attributes of the bookmark. After that, you need to pass the &lt;strong&gt;Bookmark&lt;/strong&gt; object to the &lt;strong&gt;CreateBookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; method of &lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarkEditor&lt;/strong&gt; class. Finally, you need to save the updated PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;Save&lt;/strong&gt; method. The following code snippet shows you how to add the bookmark in an existing PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/4a12f0ebd453e7f0d552ed6658ed3253.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePdfFacades-Bookmarks-AddBookmark-AddBookmark.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;add-child-bookmark-in-an-existing-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Child Bookmark in an Existing PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can add child bookmarks in an existing PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarkEditor&lt;/strong&gt; class. In order to add child bookmarks, you need to create &lt;strong&gt;Bookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; and&lt;em&gt;Bookmark&lt;/em&gt; objects. You can add individual &lt;strong&gt;Bookmark&lt;/strong&gt; objects into &lt;strong&gt;Bookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; object. You also need to create a &lt;strong&gt;Bookmark&lt;/strong&gt; object and set its &lt;strong&gt;ChildItem&lt;/strong&gt; property to &lt;strong&gt;Bookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; object. You then need to pass this &lt;strong&gt;Bookmark&lt;/strong&gt; object with &lt;strong&gt;ChildItem&lt;/strong&gt; to the &lt;strong&gt;CreateBookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; method. Finally, you need to save the updated PDF using &lt;strong&gt;Save&lt;/strong&gt; method of the &lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarkEditor&lt;/strong&gt; class. The following code snippet shows you how to add child bookmarks in an existing PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/4a12f0ebd453e7f0d552ed6658ed3253.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePdfFacades-Bookmarks-AddChildBookmark-AddChildBookmark.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Net: Import and Export Bookmarks</title>
      <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/net/import-and-export-bookmarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/net/import-and-export-bookmarks/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h2 id=&#34;import-bookmarks-from-xml-to-an-existing-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Import Bookmarks from XML to an Existing PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ImportBookmarksWithXml&lt;/strong&gt; method allows you to import bookmarks into a PDF file from an XML file. In order to import the bookmarks, you need to create &lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarkEditor&lt;/strong&gt; object and bind the PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;BindPdf&lt;/strong&gt; method. After that, you need to call &lt;strong&gt;ImportBookmarksWithXml&lt;/strong&gt; method. Finally, save the updated PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;Save&lt;/strong&gt; method. The following code snippet shows you how to import bookmarks from an XML file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/4a12f0ebd453e7f0d552ed6658ed3253.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePdfFacades-Bookmarks-ImportFromXML-ImportFromXML.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;export-bookmarks-to-xml-from-an-existing-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Export Bookmarks to XML from an Existing PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ExportBookmarksToXml method allows you to export bookmarks from a PDF file to an XML file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To export bookmarks:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a PdfBookmarkEditor object and bind the PDF file using the BindPdf method.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Call the ExportBookmarksToXml method.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Save the updated PDF file using the Save method.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following code snippet shows you how to export bookmarks to an XML file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/4a12f0ebd453e7f0d552ed6658ed3253.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePdfFacades-Bookmarks-ExportToXML-ExportToXML.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Net: Update, Delete and Get Bookmarks</title>
      <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/net/update-delete-and-get-bookmarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/net/update-delete-and-get-bookmarks/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h2 id=&#34;update-an-existing-bookmark-in-the-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update an Existing Bookmark in the PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to update an existing bookmark in a PDF file, you need to use &lt;strong&gt;ModifyBookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; method. This method takes two arguments: source title (the title of the bookmark to modify), destination title (the title to be replaced). You need to create an object of &lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarkEditor&lt;/strong&gt; class and bind input PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;BindPdf&lt;/strong&gt; method. After that, you need to call &lt;strong&gt;ModifyBookmark&lt;/strong&gt; method, and then save the updated PDF using &lt;strong&gt;Save&lt;/strong&gt; method. The following code snippet shows you how to modify an existing bookmark in a PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/4a12f0ebd453e7f0d552ed6658ed3253.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePdfFacades-Bookmarks-UpdateBookmark-UpdateBookmark.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;delete-all-bookmarks-from-the-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Delete All Bookmarks from the PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can delete all the bookmarks from the PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;DeleteBookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; method without any parameters. First of all, you need to create an object of &lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarkEditor&lt;/strong&gt; class and bind the input PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;BindPdf&lt;/strong&gt; method. After that, you need to call the &lt;strong&gt;DeleteBookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; method and then save the updated PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;Save&lt;/strong&gt; method. The following code snippet shows you how to delete all the bookmarks from the PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/4a12f0ebd453e7f0d552ed6658ed3253.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePdfFacades-Bookmarks-DeleteAllBookmarks-DeleteAllBookmarks.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;delete-a-particular-bookmark-from-a-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Delete a Particular Bookmark from a PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to delete a particular bookmark, you need to call &lt;strong&gt;DeleteBookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; method with string (title) parameter. The &lt;strong&gt;title&lt;/strong&gt; here represents the bookmark to be deleted from the PDF. Create an object of &lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarkEditor&lt;/strong&gt; class and bind input PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;BindPdf&lt;/strong&gt; method. After that, call &lt;strong&gt;DeleteBookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; method and then save the updated PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;Save&lt;/strong&gt; method. The following code snippet shows you how to delete a particular bookmark from a PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/4a12f0ebd453e7f0d552ed6658ed3253.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePdfFacades-Bookmarks-DeleteABookmark-DeleteABookmark.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-bookmarks-from-the-pdf-document-facades&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get Bookmarks from the PDF Document Facades&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarkEditor&lt;/strong&gt; class provides the feature to manipulate Bookmarks in existing PDF file. It provides various properties to get/set information regarding bookmarks. The following code snippet shows how to get information related to each bookmark in PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/4a12f0ebd453e7f0d552ed6658ed3253.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePdfFacades-Bookmarks-GetFromPDF-GetFromPDF.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;extract-bookmarks-from-an-existing-pdf-file&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Extract Bookmarks from an Existing PDF File&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ExtractBookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; method allows you to extract bookmarks from a PDF file. In order to extract the bookmarks, you need to create &lt;strong&gt;PdfBookmarkEditor&lt;/strong&gt; object and bind the PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;BindPdf&lt;/strong&gt; method. After that, you need to call &lt;strong&gt;ExtractBookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; method. The &lt;strong&gt;ExtractBookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; method returns &lt;strong&gt;Bookmarks&lt;/strong&gt; object. You can then loop through these bookmarks and get individual &lt;strong&gt;Bookmark&lt;/strong&gt; objects. Finally, save the updated PDF file using &lt;strong&gt;Save&lt;/strong&gt; method. The following code snippet shows you how to export bookmarks to an XML file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;application/javascript&#34; src=&#34;https://gist.github.com/aspose-pdf/4a12f0ebd453e7f0d552ed6658ed3253.js?file=Examples-CSharp-AsposePdfFacades-Bookmarks-ExtractBookmarks-ExtractBookmarks.cs&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
