<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation – Feature Tour</title>
    <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/jasperreports/feature-tour/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Feature Tour on Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/jasperreports/feature-tour/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jasperreports: Easy and Lightweight Deployment</title>
      <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/jasperreports/easy-and-lightweight-deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/jasperreports/easy-and-lightweight-deployment/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aspose.PDF for JasperReports is an export extension for &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.jaspersoft.com/jasperreports&#34;&gt;JasperReports&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aspose.PDF for JasperReports is provided as a single JAR file and can easily be integrated with JasperReports and JasperServer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To install Aspose.PDF for JasperReports, simply copy the &lt;strong&gt;Aspose-pdf-jasperreports.jar&lt;/strong&gt; file to the correct folder (JasperReports\lib). To integrate with JasperServer you also need to edit a JasperServer configuration file. &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/pdf/jasperreports/installation-html/&#34;&gt;Read the installation section&lt;/a&gt; for detailed installation steps.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jasperreports: Simple and Affordable Licensing</title>
      <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/jasperreports/simple-and-affordable-licensing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/jasperreports/simple-and-affordable-licensing/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;

Every Aspose license comes with 1 year of free software updates and unlimited free technical support.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aspose.PDF for JasperReports evaluation and paid versions are the same download. The trial version provides the same features as the licensed version, with the exception that it inserts an evaluation watermark in the output PDF document. You can &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.aspose.com/community/files/67/jasperreports-exporters/aspose.pdf-for-jasperreports/default.aspx&#34;&gt;download Aspose.PDF for JasperReports&lt;/a&gt; and install it. It works in evaluation mode automatically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please take an advantage of the evaluation version of Aspose.PDF for JasperReports: it does not have time limitations and comes with free technical support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Evaluation mode injects watermarks into exported reports. When you &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.aspose.com/community/forums/aspose.purchase/220/showforum.aspx&#34;&gt;buy a license&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/pdf/jasperreports/licensing-html/&#34;&gt;simply apply the license&lt;/a&gt; and watermark will no more appear in the output documents.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jasperreports: World Class Free Technical Support</title>
      <link>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/jasperreports/world-class-free-technical-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.aspose.com/pdf/jasperreports/world-class-free-technical-support/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-primary&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;

Aspose is renowned for its free and unlimited technical support provided directly by the developers of the products. If a new version of a product is available, or if resolving a question results in a fix, all new releases are free if you have an active subscription.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;getting-support&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Getting Support&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;forums&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Forums&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.aspose.com/Community/Forums/&#34;&gt;Aspose&amp;rsquo;s Support Forums&lt;/a&gt; is the place not only to resolve technical issues, but to participate in discussions with the vibrant and growing community of Aspose users. Currently there are over 190,000 users registered at the Aspose website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;blogs&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blogs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.aspose.com/Community/Blogs/&#34;&gt;Aspose.Blogs&lt;/a&gt; is the place to look for information about the latest releases and about what Aspose developers have to say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;need-more-support&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Need more support?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aspose offers free support to all users. For companies want that their issue will get prioritized, or who want to influence our product development road map, there are &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.aspose.com/corporate/services/support-options.aspx&#34;&gt;advanced support options&lt;/a&gt; like Priority Support and Enterprise Support.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
